Number one
K-content channel.
tvN for joy.
Fifteen.
THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM IS
NOT SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS PRODUCT PLACEMENTS
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISING.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS AND TOURISM
KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
THIS DRAMA
IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION
I had...
fun today.
So did I.
Listen.
Not as your CEO
but as Kang Ha-gi
I want to...
Excuse me.
TEAM MANAGER KIM MI-YOUNG
REPORTER PARK MIN-HA
- Hey, Seul-a.
- Hey!
There's a scandal about you and Chan.
There are articles
with photos of you two together.
What?
EXCLUSIVE:
LEE CHAN, DATING A STALKER FAN?
LEE CHAN SPOTTED ON A DATE WITH MS. A
A PHOTO OF A AND LEE ON A DATE
Mr. Kang.
Is this...
Is this true?
So the person you were seeing
was Chan?
Mr. Kang, you see...
Mr. Kang.
Chan.
Mr. Kang's not in.
He went to meet reporters.
Why did he release my statement
without talking to me?
- He can't just deny it.
- We needed a quick fix.
We were bombarded with calls.
Da-reum got branded
a stalker fan because of me.
You should've protected
the civilian first!
Calm down, Chan.
We just threw the fact out there.
We can explain this
in an orderly way.
What fact?
Then what could we say?
That you asked her out
but got dumped?
You're about to be cast
on Director Park's film.
Do you know how crucial this is?
What about Da-reum?
She's not a stalker fan.
Send out a press release
making that claim.
EXCLUSIVE:
LEE CHAN, DATING A STALKER FAN?
SPOTTED ON A MIDNIGHT PARK DATE
EPISODE 8
EXCLUSIVE:
LEE CHAN, DATING A STALKER FAN?
MS. A IS AN EMPLOYEE
AT LEE'S FASHION COMPANY
THEY'VE DEVELOPED FEELINGS
WHILE WORKING TOGETHER
SHE ALLEGEDLY GOT THE JOB
TO GET CLOSER TO...
Any special reason
why you came to Appello?
There was someone
I really wanted to meet.
To be honest, it wasn't a blind date.
I've liked him for a very long time.
I almost forgot.
It's from my heart.
How could I have been so delusional?
Who's this?
Has Appello explained this?
Can't believe no one at work knew.
But Chan has to go to LA.
Only he'll end up suffering.
What is going on?
What if he doesn't get the part
for Park Chan-dong's film?
It's creepy that she got a job there.
- That's so malicious.
- Chan is a victim too.
The agency denied it, so let's wait.
I doubt he knew.
She came onto him as an employee.
Me...
a stalker fan?
Shut the door.
- Won-bin.
- No, not now.
That car has been
following you from the office.
We've denied it once,
so if you get filmed here again
it'll put both you and Da-reum
in trouble.
Let's not make this any worse,
so just wait for now, Chan.
Guys, I'm here yet again
to defend justice.
I'm right here. I have arrived.
- It's right here.
- I'm finally here.
All right, everyone.
Things already look awful.
There are funeral wreaths everywhere.
Did you see
my live stream last night?
- You're right.
- I'm telling you.
Apparently, the stalker fan
applied for a job
at Lee Chan's agency, didn't get in.
So she applied to Appello instead.
My informant told me.
You're right, guys.
That's basically a stalker,
not a stalker fan.
Hey!
What are you doing
in front of our office? What's that?
Did you get permission to film here?
I am here to defend
the viewers' right to know.
You're currently obstructing
our business right now!
You're such a nuisance.
- Turn it off and go.
- What's with you?
- Wait a second.
- Go away.
- Go, now.
- Don't push.
Go.
Darn it. What's wrong with you?
- Hey!
- Go away, everyone.
That's her?
I'm not really sure.
Hi.
Hello.
You're here.
Da-reum.
- Fire the stalker fan, Appello!
- Yes.
Tell them we'll take legal action
against any false information.
I'll talk to the investors.
Why won't they leave?
Don't they have better things to do?
Jeez.
- Fire the stalker fan!
The crowd is getting bigger.
Our customer service is stumped
because of complaints
and our investors just called too.
The knot event is around the corner.
So if Nam Da-reum takes charge
those clout chasers will be there
given the current situation.
She'd be canceled publicly.
There's no evidence
that she's a stalker fan.
Also, you all know
how hard she had worked
to move this forward.
But that's not
what the public will think.
We should probably announce
the company's official statement
regarding Ms. Nam.
I'll check the facts first.
Also, prepare the event
with the worst-case scenario in mind.
- Yes, sir.
Hello? Yes.
I'm sorry. I was in a meeting.
Hello?
Yes, I see.
Yes.
Did you see
the company's social media account?
Yes, what do we do?
Ms. Da-reum might see it soon.
- Young-woo.
- Yes?
Don't we have to upload
the pop-up's second announcement?
Right, I'll do that, Da-reum.
What?
But I'm in charge of that, so why?
Well...
It's probably best
if you don't read it for a while.
UNFRAMED: KNOTTING
UNTYING TRADITIONS TO TIE IT ANEW
- Fire the stalker fan!
- Cancel Appello!
ARE YOU LOOKING
TO RUIN YOUR BUSINESS?
THE CEO IS OUT OF HIS MIND TOO
AN EVENT BY A STALKER FAN? INSANE
DON'T WANT NO EVENT
WITH A STALKER FAN
WHAT'S THE CEO DOING?
EXPLAIN YOURSELF
APPELLO, A BUSINESS FOR STALKER FANS
UNTIE THAT STALKER FAN FIRST
Tear it apart.
ON MY WAY TO THROW AWAY MY CLOTHES
Ms. Da-reum.
Are you all right?
Mr. Kang wants to talk to you.
Okay.
I'll be there.
Come in.
Ms. Nam.
Please be honest.
You said you applied for a job here
because you wanted to meet someone.
And you said you recently met
your long-time crush.
Yes.
Were you
referring to Director Lee?
Yes, I had been his fan
for a very long time.
But I really am not a stalker fan.
- Please believe me.
- You're saying
it's true you joined Appello
because of Director Lee.
I started dreaming of becoming
a fashion marketer because of him.
And of course,
I wanted to learn and work here.
Director Lee and I are not
in the kind of relationship
that people think.
You went on a date...
but you're not dating?
Fine.
I'll cross-examine with Director Lee
before I make my decision.
You may leave.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
NAME: NAM DA-REUM
I'm sorry.
That is
the only thing I can do
for the company at the moment.
Once I leave
they'll stop protesting
and boycotting us.
I don't want to be
a nuisance to the company.
I understand what you mean.
As of this moment
you will be on standby
at home, not in the office.
Boycott Appello!
- Boycott Appello!
Fire the stalker fan!
- Kick her out!
Boycott Appello!
- Boycott Appello!
Fire the stalker fan!
- Fire her!
Boycott Appello!
- Boycott Appello!
Kick out the stalker fan!
- Kick her out!
Fire the stalker fan!
- Fire her!
Boycott Appello!
- Boycott Appello!
Fire the stalker fan!
- Fire her!
Boycott Appello!
- Boycott Appello!
Fire the stalker fan!
- Fire her!
Boycott Appello!
- Boycott Appello!
Fire the stalker fan!
- Fire her!
Boycott Appello!
- Boycott Appello!
Fire the stalker fan!
- Fire her!
Fire her without excuse!
Boycott Appello!
- Boycott Appello!
- Fire the stalker fan!
- She's walking out!
- Is that her?
- Are you the one?
- Are you dating Lee Chan?
- It's you?
We have so many questions.
- Can you look here?
- Did you admit to being a stalker?
- Say something.
Will you say something?
Just say anything!
Is everything true?
Hey, talk to us.
- Say something.
- Come on.
- Talk.
- Stop filming!
She's not a criminal.
Did she do anything wrong?
They aren't dating.
What's wrong with everyone?
Fine, so move aside
so she can explain herself.
I don't care.
Don't you dare film her.
I'll sue every single one of you.
- Move aside.
- Film her.
- Move!
- Show us your face!
I said, stop!
- What?
- What was that?
Get lost, you stalker.
Stop immediately.
Otherwise, I will see you
at the police station.
Let's go.
FIRE THE STALKER FAN IMMEDIATELY
- Move back.
- Please step back.
Please move.
Are you all right?
- Yes.
- Mr. Kang.
So...
About Ms. Da-reum's resignation.
Do you plan to actually process it?
Ask our attorney to come in.
Sure, Mr. Kang.
I just want to go home.
Hey, don't be so weak.
Woman,
we didn't bring you up like this.
I just want to be alone today.
And all you'll do
is mope on the floor.
You have to party on a day like this.
Party? What kind of party?
Ta-da.
A binge-eating party.
Just clear your mind and eat today.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- I'll pay with this.
Sure.
Let's go.
You have something... Never mind.
- That'll be 21,500 won.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- What are you doing?
- What?
- Are you coming in?
- I am.
They're not him.
VISITOR
All right.
I look perfect, as always.
Come quickly, Attorney Kim Min-woo.
Yes, coming.
CELEBRITY BULLETIN BOARD
"More funeral wreaths
arriving at Appello."
Jeez. It's a whole mess.
Because of Chan's big scandal
I couldn't even go to Pilates.
He's never helpful.
As our attorney
what's the solution?
When it comes to risk control
it would be the fastest
to process her resignation.
But if you wish to keep her on board
sue the hate comments for defamation
under the Information and
Communications Network Act
and the illegal protesters
for obstruction of business
under Article 314
of the Criminal Act.
We may win legally
but public opinion
against Appello could worsen, right?
Probably.
- We got lots of clams for the pasta.
- Yes.
These all look great today.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Hey, did you see him?
Her CEO took her in his arms
and got egged instead.
"Stop immediately."
That was so cool.
- Even my heart skipped a beat.
- Tell me about it.
Hey.
Focus on eating.
No other thoughts allowed.
Do you two also think
I am
a stalker fan?
- Namda.
- I am a fan.
And I did get a job at his company.
Anyone can see
that this is premeditated.
Mr. Kang probably
thinks of me that way too.
- Hey.
- I mean
everyone calls me a stalker fan.
It feels like all those years
I've spent as a fan
have been tainted too.
Come on.
Who cares what others say?
You're not like that.
I mean, if that's the case
are fans not allowed to get a job?
She worked hard
to get a job at a place she wanted.
How is that a crime?
CELEBRITY FORUM
What is this?
KINDA BLURRED BUT GOT A SHOT OF HER
ACCESS DENIED:
THIS POST HAS BEEN REPORTED
CAME TO APPELLO AND SAW THE GIRL
ACCESS DENIED:
THIS POST HAS BEEN REPORTED
What a relief.
But who reported these posts?
Gosh. It's been so long
since I've worked that hard.
Great work.
Anyway...
Do you have to go this far?
What?
Must you take everyone down
so mercilessly?
Hey.
Jeez.
Why, you...
Do you know what we had
to go through because of you?
We need to talk.
I'll talk to you later.
What about Da-reum?
"Da-reum"?
So you'll stop pretending
in front of me now?
Was she okay at work today?
Where's your responsibility
as the company's director?
Look at what it has come to.
I'm sorry.
A correction will be issued soon.
Do you think saying sorry is enough?
What about the hundreds of people
at Appello?
Have you thought of them?
Da-reum and I...
aren't dating.
And she's not a stalker fan.
I didn't want you to misunderstand.
You've already
blown this way out of proportion.
The company lost its trust,
and Da-reum got publicly humiliated.
She's now branded
and suffering from insults.
At the very least
you should've told me.
What about you?
Do you tell me everything?
I heard about your mother's accident
from another person.
What about Jeong-yeon?
Were you honest when I asked
how you felt about Da-reum?
Hey.
Do you even think of me as a friend?
If investors keep pressuring you,
I'll step down.
I'll take responsibility.
"Responsibility"?
Then put out this fire
you've started.
Boycott Appello!
- Boycott Appello!
Kick out the obsessive fan!
- Kick her out!
Boycott Appello!
- Boycott Appello!
I mean, is Director Lee Chan
even thinking right now?
SE Corporation is
advertising to the world
that they're opening
their fashion platform soon.
How can he cause
a boycott at this time?
Yes, we're aware.
I understand your anxiety
as investors
but give us a little more time.
After the correction report,
things are dying down...
What are you talking about?
They're making a scene out there!
How can the company's value falter
just because of one employee?
Yes, realistically speaking,
if she's our risk at the moment
they must get rid of her.
- Fire her.
- Do that.
Are you asking us
to give in to the public sentiment
even though
the allegations weren't factual?
Don't you know
the words "emotional damage"?
When consumers don't like something,
you must always grovel.
Grovel? That is so wrong.
We released a correction report.
Now, settle down.
- People are boycotting you.
- That's not it.
That'll settle this for now.
And then what?
- Fire her!
Fire the stalker fan!
Boycott Appello!
Then we will be shaken
whenever something like this happens
and even abandon
someone important to us.
Mr. Kang.
This isn't the time
to discuss your idealism.
I am talking about standards.
Ms. Nam is a competent employee
who performed well during her time.
Shouldn't we see this as a management
issue, not an individual one?
- What now?
- How can he say that?
No matter what the decision is
I will take responsibility.
- Responsibility?
- He will?
I am the one leading Appello
and I've already proven it
with our performances.
All right.
The opening of SE's platform
will be your testing ground.
We'll see
if you can still keep your position.
I will show you
with the results.
Mr. Kang.
Are you sure about this?
What?
I think I understand
the decision you have made.
Then be my support.
Mr. Kang.
Yes, I will do that
as one of your employees.
But let me say this as a friend.
Ha-gi, if this continues
your position as the CEO
will be in jeopardy.
Let me see the investors off.
There are so many things to do.
I hope
the preparations are going well.
I mean
my absence won't have an impact
on the company as a whole.
MASTER IM CHEONG-RIM
Hello, Master Im.
Hello, Ms. Nam.
This is Im Cheong-rim calling.
Yes, please speak, ma'am.
How is the preparation going
for the event?
Of course. I was just busy
because of the preparations.
MS. NAM DA-REUM
Have you received
the project proposal and the samples?
Well, it wasn't half bad.
She loves that she gets to do
the event with Lee Chan.
Quiet.
Anyway.
I wanted to share some of my input,
so I sent you an email.
I'll be in Seoul in a few days,
so we'll talk more then.
Right. Yes, I'll check my email.
Yes. Goodbye.
What do I do?
Get it together, Da-reum.
This is not the time for this.
REVISION REQUEST
FOR APPELLO'S SHOWROOM
I ATTACH MY REVISIONS BELOW
SEE YOU SOON IN SEOUL
Come in.
Mr. Kang.
Master Im must've sent her feedback.
Da-reum put together her requests
and sent them over.
Please check your email.
- Okay.
- All right.
POP-UP REVISIONS, MEETING IN SEOUL
THIS IS NAM DA-REUM OF MARKETING
KNOTTING SHOWROOM REVISION REPORT
NAM DA-REUM
TOP VIEW OF THE SHOWROOM
WITH MASTER IM'S REVISION REQUESTS
Let's do this together.
You've got to smile
when things get tough.
Don't you know
smiling actually makes things better?
But Mom.
It's a small company.
I feel...
like I can be of use here.
That's why I like Appello
and I'm happier here.
I don't want to be
a nuisance to the company.
CEO KANG HA-GI
The office feels so empty
without Da-reum.
She always spread
positive energy at work.
I know.
I really miss Da-reum.
She looked like she was barely
eating these days.
I wonder if she's going to be okay.
We have to worry
about the event first.
- I'm completely clueless.
- Me neither.
Should we ask Da-reum for help?
Shall we?
Let's do that.
POST
Reporter Do Eun-young is
the one who first reported it.
Sort it out in person.
You can do that much.
Yes, the massage felt especially
good today.
Oh, no need to thank me.
I should thank you for the scoop
on the scandal.
I...
I'll call you back.
I read your article,
Reporter Do Eun-young.
Doesn't Cho-yi come here too?
You must be rich.
A luxury spa membership
and the latest designer items.
You really went all out.
So you knew everything
before you came.
If you could
publish a series
of exclusives like this
you two must be pretty close.
So?
Why are you here?
You need to publish
a correction article.
She's not a stalker fan.
Corrections are made only
when the article is clearly false.
Because it is clearly false
I came here to tell you in person.
What if I say no?
I've got a tip-off for you too.
"Following the article's publication
are luxury spa treatments
and designer gifts."
How does that sound?
Is an actor threatening the press?
Because I am an actor.
If I open my mouth,
it'll cause quite an impact.
Maybe I can try adjusting the tone.
Without the word "stalker fan."
I want a correction
not an adjustment.
QUICK DELIVERY
HIRING DELIVERY DRIVERS
He should've been here at least once.
Where is everyone?
There are so many calls. Jeez.
Gosh.
- Is this the one calling?
- Yes, that's right.
But I'm starving.
- I don't even have time to eat.
- Hurry up and get going.
Hurry.
Oh, jeez.
Excuse me.
Among the delivery drivers here...
- What took you so long?
- What?
This is perfect.
You have a helmet.
Are you using a bicycle?
I parked my bicycle right outside.
Delivery by bicycle isn't so bad.
- No, I...
- It's all in the neighborhood.
- You'll be fine.
- No.
- It's not so hard.
- That's not why I'm here.
It's Fiery Chicken Feet
by the intersection.
Go as fast as you can.
- Okay?
- Wait. That's not why I'm here.
- I'm here to find someone...
- Okay. I hear you.
- I need to find someone...
- Okay. All right.
Will you please listen to me?
I won't charge you fees for now.
Thank you.
No, sir. Wait...
Bye-bye.
FIERY CHICKEN FEET
If he doesn't show up,
I'll go find him.
Roy, if you're not coming,
I'll go to you.
Wait for me!
FIERY CHICKEN FEET
APPELLO CARES MORE ABOUT STALKER FANS
THAN LEE CHAN'S SAFETY
It feels like
I shouldn't be here.
APPELLO CARES MORE ABOUT STALKER FANS
THAN LEE CHAN'S SAFETY
- Did you mean this?
- Yes.
- Don't say anything.
- What?
- Min-a...
- Shush.
- Don't say a word.
- What?
Wait. What are you doing?
Ta-da.
- Da-reum, I missed you so much.
- We were so worried about you.
Me too. I missed you so much.
I was actually worried about this.
Let me explain Master Im's requests
and the updated route.
I applied Master Im's requests
to the design.
Especially here.
- The demonstration space...
- Ms. Da-reum.
How can you worry about the company
after all that?
What about you?
After spending a few days at home
I realized
waking up in the morning for work
made me happy.
I tried not to think about the event,
but I just couldn't.
Typical of you.
How is...
Mr. Kang?
Mr. Kang doesn't really talk much.
He's been working even harder.
I don't know what he's thinking.
INGUK STATION
What am I doing here?
Mr. Kang?
What brings you here?
I...
I was on my way home.
You pass this way?
Yeah, well...
We live in the same neighborhood,
after all.
It's only normal for us
to run into each other.
Anyway...
I'm on my way home.
Have you been well?
Yeah, well...
What about you?
Have you been well?
No.
If...
you're here to see me
feel free to talk to me, Mr. Kang.
What do you mean?
I won't blame you
even if you fire me.
I submitted my resignation
to take responsibility.
It's best for the company
to make an official...
What are you saying?
I've been
sorting out my feelings.
I'll be okay.
Why do you say that
when you're not okay?
Is that how someone who's okay looks?
You're here to say it anyway.
I'm here because I missed you.
I came because I was worried.
Happy now?
It's late.
You should go home.
Bye.
He missed me?
MR. KANG
MR. KANG SHOWED UP OUTSIDE MY HOUSE
FINALLY MY FIRST DAY AT APPELLO
PROJECT OUTSTANDING EMPLOYEE
BECOME MR. KANG'S SECRET AGENT
MR. KANG
FIRST OUTSIDE MEETING WITH MR. KANG
I ALMOST SLIPPED,
BUT MR. KANG HELD ME
MR. KANG HELD AN UMBRELLA OVER ME
MR. KANG
I CAN'T STOP THINKING ABOUT MR. KANG
HE SAID IT WAS NICE TO SEE ME AGAIN
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Why...
I only wrote about Mr. Kang.
Mr. Kang. Why are you
so serious about this?
We have a goal. We want Jjak.
Kung and Jjak left
but you can still contact me
for no reason.
What's wrong with me?
Reporter Do Eun-young
won't be coming.
I got her
something bigger than you did.
Cho-yi.
Stop crossing the line.
That's what I'm here to say.
What?
If you mess with her again
I won't let it slide.
So?
Are you doing this to me
to protect that one girl?
Chan, get a hold of yourself.
Do you know
how much that degraded you?
What if you got involved
in a scandal with me?
Well, people will still be jealous.
But people would've said
we made a good couple.
But what about her?
People did nothing but criticize.
- Yoon Cho-yi...
- I told you.
You should date someone
on your level.
You two
would only cause harm
to each other. Got it?
It's up to me to deal with it
and it's up to me to decide.
Don't mess with Da-reum.
This is my last warning.
Hey.
Lee Chan!
Are we ready?
Lee Chan is here with us today.
- Thanks for the exclusive interview.
- Yes.
First, let's start with your opinion
on the recent issue.
I should've known better
as a public figure.
She was...
never a stalker fan.
She's a fan who cares about me
just like all my other fans
but she's also my co-worker.
Nothing more, nothing less?
That's correct.
I hope loving someone
doesn't become a reason
to be criticized.
And I hope everyone stops
criticizing her.
Any word for your fans?
I'm sorry, and thank you.
I cherish the time
you spent loving me.
Thanks to all your love,
I could be where I am today.
I hope we continue
to support each other...
and stay on good terms.
KNOT
Just as you requested
we prepared the display, story,
and the experience zones.
We also made changes to the kit.
We've arranged it to reflect the idea
of Appello continuing
the tradition of your knot.
Where's Ms. Nam Da-reum?
It's her day off today.
We promised to teach her a new knot.
We picked the wrong day, Master Im.
Perhaps because I kept pushing her
she did a good job.
Tell her she did well.
Yes, Master Im.
Master Im, will you check
the exhibition display?
- Sure.
- Right...
You look gaunt.
You must've gone through a lot.
No.
I feel bad for leaving the team
before the event.
When are you
going to come back to work?
How can I do that?
There are still so many people
criticizing the company
because of me.
Everyone knows
that you're not a stalker fan now.
I asked myself
whether I had joined Appello
with pure intentions.
Then I thought
that might not be the case.
I was childish enough to think
I could see him up close
if I worked here.
You probably
wouldn't understand though.
Why is that childish?
I...
understand how you feel
better than anyone else.
You want to get as close as you can
to your favorite star
and you're willing
to do anything for him.
Actually
I was a fan of Director Lee.
What? You?
Yes.
In fact, I was the first president
of the D-Angel fandom.
Then are you...
D-Angel's legendary first president
who fought off the haters 17 to 1
and wiped them out completely
in D.N.X's early days?
Was that really you?
It wasn't 17 to 1.
It was 19 to 1 to be exact.
No way.
You're the one
who created D-Angel's fan culture.
But how did you start working
at Appello...
When Director Lee first opened
the concept store
he recruited me.
At the time, I was working
at a fashion company.
I can't say
I didn't have
any other motives at first.
Working with the star we admire
feels surreal to us.
His success feels like my success.
But over time, I realized
what really matters is...
who I am.
It's about what I find fun
and what I want to be good at.
I'm sure
you had the same concerns.
Speaking of which
you should come back to work.
Why would you run away
when you didn't do anything wrong?
You're the most passionate,
and you work harder than anyone else.
Everyone is
waiting for you.
I wish
I could go back.
But that
would put Mr. Kang in trouble.
Haven't you seen it yet?
Seen what?
Mr. Kang posted
Appello's official statement.
What?
Actually, I'm here
because Mr. Kang asked me.
He asked me to give you this knot.
Do you have any idea
how much he was worried about you?
APPELLO OFFICIAL STATEMENT
Appello has verified the facts
regarding the matter
involving one of our employees.
We confirm that the employee
in question is not a stalker fan.
In fact, the employee in question is
a dedicated and responsible member
who has been faithfully carrying out
her duties at Appello.
And yet
some fans are pressuring
the employee in question to resign
based on claims
that have been found to be false.
- I knew he'd do it.
- See? He's good.
Hey. Be quiet.
Appello will not give in
to any unreasonable demands
nor will we tolerate
any slander or threats
against our employee.
APPELLO'S CEO HANDLED THIS WITH CLASS
I FEEL BAD FOR THEIR ROOKIE
THAT IS WHAT A TRUE LEADER IS
GOING ALL IN ON APPELLO STOCKS
The employee in question will
remain a member of Appello
as she has always been.
Ms. Nam.
What brings you here at this hour?
Did you run here?
Yes.
But it's cold.
Mr. Kang. I...
I don't want to quit.
But why? You already submitted
your resignation.
Because of you.
You made me work
even outside the office.
It's unfair.
You said I'd remain
a member of Appello
as I have always been.
I'm sorry...
the official statement took so long.
To repay your trust
I'll dedicate myself to Appello.
Because I'm a CEO
I always have to hold back
before making a decision.
I have to think twice
and hesitate countless times.
I'm not even as brave as you think.
It must've been hard on you...
hasn't it?
No.
I'm sorry.
From now on
I'm not going to hide
my feelings anymore.
I'm going to be honest
about everything.
I don't want to say
that I won't blame you
even if you fire me...
or that I'm okay.
I missed Appello.
I missed my job.
And...
what's more...
I missed you.
I think...
I...
like you, Mr. Kang.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
"Making money by being a stalker fan.
What an easy life."
Hey. How about this?
It breaches both the Network Act
and criminal law.
Request a takedown first.
We need a warrant
to identify the person.
Taking screenshots of everything.
Good.
Now we send
the notice to the platforms
then the posts
will be deleted tonight.
Okay.
"The company must go down
for hiring a stalker."
Screenshot that too.
"Maybe the stalker is
gaslighting Lee Chan."
I'm reporting it.
"That's not a stalker.
She's living the dream life."
"She even landed a job."
Is that a compliment
or a hate comment?
- Hey. Let that slide.
- Let it slide?
Yeah.
"I actually saw the stalker fan.
She wasn't that pretty."
Delete that false information.
She's pretty in person.
FOR
FOR REAL
Delete the false information.
She's pretty for real.
No matter how hard things get,
don't let go of my hand.
This is crazy.
Secret office romance rules.
Da-reum.
No touching.
You look happy.
Why Ha-gi and not me?
It's the hottest topic
in fashion right now.
The Creative Director's identity is
under wraps.
Let's bring Han on board.
She's on her way now.
Do you need my help?
See if you can win Ha-gi's heart.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Kang Ha-gi.
Subtitles by Eunjin Erica Kim
and Jennifer Jean Lim
Synced and corrected by
WEISSACHsubs